# Muh Roby Setiawan

Passionate Software Developer specializing in front-end web and mobile development

0812-7306-7776 robysetiawan2409@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/muh-roby-setiawan https://robysetiawan.vercel.app

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

I am a seasoned Full Stack Web and Mobile Developer with over 6 years of experience in delivering exceptional digital solutions. My expertise spans a wide range of technologies including HTML/CSS, JavaScript, PHP, TypeScript, and frameworks such as React, Next.js, and Nuxt.js for web development, while for mobile development, I specialize in Flutter, React Native, and native iOS development. I have a proven track record of developing user-friendly websites and mobile applications that meet and exceed client expectations. I am committed to continuous learning and innovation in the everevolving field of technology.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Oxy Creative / Jakarta - Jan 2021 - Mar 2024

- Developed a Private Swift Framework for SDK creation, iOS applications using UIKit and SwiftUI, and plugins for Flutter and React Native. And develop app for client, and app demo for private frameworks
- Successfully published apps on the App Store and plugins on CocoaPods.
- Created comprehensive documentation for plugins and SDKs.
- Utilized smart design techniques to optimize SaaS systems for efficiency and scalability.

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER – PT. Djelas Tanda Tangan Bersama / Jakarta – Jun 2021 – Feb 2024

- Part of OXY Creative's Outsource Team.
- Developed mobile applications using flutter, and nuxt.js and collaborate with API services team.
- Orchestrated the seamless migration of services to new technology stacks.
- Orchestrated the design and implementation of databases for optimal performance and seamless functionality.
- Executed ongoing maintenance tasks with precision and efficiency, ensuring the highest standards of quality and user satisfaction.

#### WEB LARAVEL DEVELOPER - PT Kreasi Arduo Indonesia / Tangerang - Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

- Conducting proactive maintenance initiatives and seamlessly integrating new features into applications to enhance functionality and user experience
- Skillfully designing robust databases and translating intricate application requirements into efficient and scalable solutions..
- Maintaining existing menus on the admin dashboard.
- Adding new sections to the homepage and resolving bugs.

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER - PT. DHD Mitra Indotama / Palembang - Jan 2020 - Sep 2020

- Developed the backend (REST API) and front-end website, including the admin side, for a startup mobile app using Codelgniter.
- Created mobile applications using Flutter for the startup app.
- Implemented robust and scalable solutions to meet the app's requirements.
- Ensured seamless integration between the frontend and backend systems for optimal performance.
- Collaborated with the team to deliver high-quality software within the project timelines.
- Contributed to the design and architecture of the app to ensure its scalability and maintainability.

# **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSITY BINA DARMA- Palembang – Sep 2016 - Jul 2019

Associate degree in Information Management

#### **SKILLS**

## Language Skills

Framework Skills

Typescript, JavaScript, Php, Dart, Swift

Flutter, React native, Swift, React.js, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel, Codelgniter

## Languages

Bilingual in Indonesia and English.